A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Administration, Building Services, Ford Foundation Headquarters, New Building Planning and Construction Files FA500
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Construction Files, Bulk, 1963-1969 1959-1971 (bulk 1963-1969); 1963-1969; III (Box not specified)
  - Reports -- Concrete Pours -- Phase I -- R.W. Hunt (1 of 10), Jan 25-May 12, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Reports -- Concrete Pours -- Phase I -- R.W. Hunt (2 of 10), May 19-Aug 5, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Reports -- Concrete Test Cylinder -- R.W. Hunt (3 of 10), Aug 19-Dec 21, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Reports -- Concrete Test Cylinder -- R.W. Hunt (4 of 10), Dec 2, 1965-Mar 24, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Reports -- Concrete Test Cylinder -- R.W. Hunt (5 of 10), Mar 2-May 20, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Reports -- Concrete Test Cylinder -- R.W. Hunt (6 of 10), Apr 27-Jul 14, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Reports -- Concrete Test Cylinder -- R.W. Hunt (7 of 10), Jun 10-Aug 31, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Reports -- Concrete Test Cylinder -- R.W. Hunt (8 of 10), Sep 15-Nov 22, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Reports -- Concrete Test Cylinder -- R.W. Hunt (9 of 10), Dec 12, 1966-Mar 14, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Reports -- Concrete Test Cylinder -- R.W. Hunt (10 of 10), Mar 20-Nov 30, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Reports -- Daily Construction (1 of 10), Nov 2, 1964-Mar 10, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Reports -- Daily Construction (2 of 10), Mar 11-Jul 22, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Reports -- Daily Construction (3 of 10), Jul 23-Dec 31, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Reports -- Daily Construction (4 of 10), Jan 3-May 14, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Reports -- Daily Construction (5 of 10), May 16-Aug 31, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Reports -- Daily Construction (6 of 10), Sep 1-Dec 30, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Reports -- Daily Construction (7 of 10), Jan 3-May 26, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Reports -- Daily Construction (8 of 10), May 27-Sep 6, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Reports -- Daily Construction (9 of 10), Sep 7-Dec 29, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Reports -- Daily Construction (10 of 10), Jan 1-Dec 31, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Reports -- Excavation Inspection, Aug 26, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Reports -- Final Mechanical Inspection, Mar 26, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Reports -- Final Report on the New Building, Jun 1970 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Reports -- Heat Exchangers -- Certificate of Inspection, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Reports -- Mechanical Inspection -- Cosentini Associates, Mar 28, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Reports -- Re-examination Report with Opinion and Estimate -- 800 Second Avenue -- John V. Dinan [photos separated], Sep 20, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Reports -- Re-examination Report with Opinion and Estimate -- 328-334 East 43rd St. Hermitage -- John V. Dinan [photos separated], Sep 20, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Reports -- Re-examination Report with Opinion -- Park West and South Walls -- John V. Dinan, Sep 30, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Reports -- Structural Design Analysis -- Severud & Associates (1 of 4), 1964 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Reports -- Structural Design Analysis -- Severud & Associates (2 of 4), 1964 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Reports -- Structural Design Analysis -- Severud & Associates (3 of 4), 1964 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Reports -- Structural Design Analysis -- Severud & Associates (4 of 4), 1964 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Reports -- Structural Steel Inspection -- Gulick-Henderson -- Transmittal Letters and Field Inspection, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Reports -- Structural Steel Inspection -- Gulick-Henderson -- Field Welding (1 of 2), Dec 30, 1965-Sep 7, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Reports -- Structural Steel Inspection -- Gulick-Henderson -- Field Welding (2 of 2), Sep 9, 1966-Aug 1, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Reports -- Structural Steel Inspection -- Gulick-Henderson -- Shop Welding, Nov 5, 1965-Nov 11, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Reports -- Surveying -- Earl B. Lovell-S.P. Belcher Inc., Dec 21, 1965-Jul 15, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Reports -- Ultrasonic Inspection -- Gulick-Henderson, Jul 24, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Reports -- Sub-surface Investigations, Sep 24-25, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Reports -- Vibration Study for Turner Construction Co. (1 of 4), Dec 21-28, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Reports -- Vibration Study for Turner Construction Co. (2 of 4), Jan 7-Feb 5, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Reports -- Vibration Study for Turner Construction Co. (3 of 4), Feb 15-Mar 19, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Reports -- Vibration Study for Turner Construction Co. (4 of 4), Mar 22-May 18, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Reports -- Vibration Study of Blasting -- John V. Dinan Consulting Engineers, May 11-15, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Resilient Flooring -- Hercules Flooring Co., 1967-1968 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Revolving Doors, Faceplates, Key Stations, etc. -- General Bronze Corp. (1 of 2), 1965-1968 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Revolving Doors, Faceplates, Key Stations, etc. -- General Bronze Corp. (2 of 2), 1965-1968 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Rolling Shutters -- The Abbotsford Co. (Crawford Door) -- Contract and Correspondence Re: Bidding, 1966-1969 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Roll-up Doors -- The Kinnear Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1965-1966 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Roofing and Flashings -- Tuttle Roofing -- Sketch and Background, Mar 7, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Room Finish Schedules, 1965-1966 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Rubbish Removal -- P&F Trucking -- Contracts, 1965-1967 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Scaffolding -- Harsco Corp., May 2, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Schedules, 1965-1966 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Schedules -- Memoranda Re: Completion Schedule, Mar 21-Jul 7, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Sidewalk Bridges -- Richard C. Mugler Co., Inc. -- Contract, Work Authorization, etc., 1965-1966 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Sketches -- Ford Foundation Headquarters -- Miscellaneous, 1965-1967 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Sketches -- Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Skylight -- Fisher Skylight Inc. -- Bidding, Contract, Work Authorization, etc., 1965-1968 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Slate -- Friedman Marble & Slate Works, Inc. -- Approved Sketches, Jan 16-30, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Slate -- Friedman Marble & Slate Works, Inc. -- Bidding, Contract, Change Orders, 1966-1968 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Snow Melting -- Correspondence, Memoranda, Background Re: Installing Sidewalk Snow Melting Coils, Jul 7, 1965-Jan 30, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Sprinkler System -- J.L. Murphy Inc. -- Equipment List, Oct 8, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Sprinkler System -- J.L. Murphy Inc. -- Bids, Contract, Work Authorization, etc., 1965-1967 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Steel Inspection -- Gulick-Henderson Testing Labs, 1966-1968 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Strikes -- Plumbers & Derrick Operators -- News Clippings and Memoranda, Aug 8, 1966-Oct 2, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Structural -- American Bridge Division -- Bolt Orders and Sketches, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Structural -- American Bridge Division -- Building Enclosure -- Drawings, Dec 21, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Structural -- American Bridge Division -- Camber in Steel Beams, Feb 2, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Structural -- American Bridge Division -- Correspondence Re: Specification Approval, Aug 3, 1965-Jun 6, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Structural -- American Bridge Division -- KO-674/KO-675 -- Illustrations, 1965-1967 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Structural -- American Bridge Division -- Plans, Oct 31, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Structural -- American Bridge Division -- Plans, Nov 1965 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Structural Concrete -- C.E. Youngdahl & Co., 1965-1966 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Subcontractors -- C.E. Youngdahl & Co. -- Contract, Correspondence, Change Orders, etc. (1 of 2), 1965-1970 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Subcontractors -- C.E. Youngdahl & Co. -- Contract, Correspondence, Change Orders, etc. (2 of 2), 1965-1970 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Subcontractors -- General Conditions, Nov 27, 1964-Apr 20, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Subcontractors -- List, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Subcontractors -- Port-O-San Corp. -- Correspondence Re: Subcontract, Dec 3, 1964-Aug 31, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Subcontractors and Suppliers -- Prospective, 1964-1965 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Subcontractors -- Surveying -- Correspondence Re: Contract, Jul 19, 1963-Dec 17, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Subcontractors -- Thomas Crimmins -- Contract with Turner Construction Co., Dec 1, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Telephone Equipment Rooms -- Memoranda Re: Phone System, Background, 1963-1968 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Telephone Facilities -- Correspondence, Notes, Order Information, Background, 1965-1970 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Trustee Budget Report -- Cost Analysis of Building Construction, Mar 1, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Trustees Building Committee -- Correspondence (1 of 3), Oct 15, 1964-Dec 9, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Trustees Building Committee -- Correspondence (2 of 3), Dec 2, 1965-Feb 17, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Trustees Building Committee -- Correspondence (3 of 3), Feb 23-Dec 29, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Trustees Building Committee -- Meetings -- Reports (1 of 3), 1963-1967 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Trustees Building Committee -- Meetings -- Delegation, Bids, Miscellaneous Cost Figures (2 of 3), 1964-1965 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Trustees Building Committee -- Meetings -- New Delhi Building -- Progress Reports (3 of 3), 1965-1970 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Trustees Building Committee -- Minutes, Notes and Memoranda, Jan 20, 1964-Jun 15, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Trustees Building Committee -- Purchase of 328 East 43rd Street, Miscellaneous Correspondence, Minutes, etc., 1964-1965 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Copies of SIS Volume I, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Approval Letters, Apr 8-Sep 20, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Budget Report, 1966-1969 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Building Construction Job Meetings -- Minutes (1 of 6), Jan 26-Nov 9, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Building Construction Job Meetings -- Minutes (2 of 6), Nov 23, 1965-Apr 7, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Building Construction Job Meetings -- Minutes (3 of 6), Apr 21-Sep 23, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Building Construction Job Meetings -- Minutes (4 of 6), Oct 13, 1966-Feb 21, 1967 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Building Construction Job Meetings -- Minutes (5 of 6), Mar 9-Jul 6, 1967 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Building Construction Job Meetings -- Minutes (6 of 6), Jul 20, 1967-Jan 15, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Building Design -- Minutes (1 of 3), 1963-1964 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Building Design -- Minutes (2 of 3), 1964-1965 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Building Design -- Minutes (3 of 3), 1966-1968 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Correspondence, 1965-1968 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Daily Report and Progress Schedule, Apr 27, 1968-Jan 13, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Management Contract (1 of 2), 1963-1965 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Management Contract (2 of 2), 1963-1965 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Management Contractor -- Correspondence Re: Contract Documents (1 of 3), Aug 1, 1963-Sep 13, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Management Contractor -- Correspondence Re: Contract Documents (2 of 3), Sep 17, 1965-Jul 8, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Management Contractor -- Correspondence Re: Contract Documents (3 of 3), Jul 15, 1966-Aug 4, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Punch List -- Meeting Minutes, Memoranda, etc. (1 of 2), Dec 18, 1967-Sep 19, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Punch List -- Floor plans (2 of 2), Dec 21, 1967-Jan 13, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Schedule of Field Operations -- Construction Schedule (1 of 2), 1967 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Schedule of Field Operations -- Construction Schedule (2 of 2), 1967 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Sketches (1 of 2), 1965 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Sketches (2 of 2), 1966-1969 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Unit Prices -- H.L. Lazar Inc. -- Re: Alteration in New Building, Jul 24, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Vertical Conveyor Work -- Lamson Corp., 1965 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Waterproofing and Damp-Proofing -- Munro Waterproofing -- Contract, Bids, etc., 1965-1967 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Window Blinds -- International Building Products, 1966-1967 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Window Washing Equipment -- Plans and Board of Standards and Appeals Ruling, Sep 30-Dec 30, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Window Washing Equipment -- Western Gear Co. -- Skyclimber -- Requirements, Change Order, Resolution, Correspondence Re: Contract and Government Approval, Maintenance Contract, etc. (1 of 3), 1966-1969 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Window Washing Equipment -- Western Gear Co. -- Skyclimber -- Correspondence Re: Contract and Government Approval, Background etc. (2 of 3), 1968-1969 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Window Washing Equipment -- Western Gear Co. -- Skyclimber -- Maintenance Contract, Permit Approvals, Correspondence, etc. (3 of 3), 1969 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Wood Flooring -- Klepp Wood Flooring Corp., 1966-1968 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Work Authorizations, 1964-1966 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Work Drawings and Specifications, 1964-1965 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Equipment and Furnishings, 1961-1969; IV (Box not specified)
  Series IV. Equipment and Furnishing, 1961-1969
  The files in this series document the outfitting of the building interior, the purchase of furniture, and the acquisition of moveable equipment. The earliest files contain information about the demonstration of experimental furniture designs by seven different possible vendors intended for the new building (1964-1965), painting estimates (1965), and the disposal of old furniture (1966-1967). Other files pertain to the planning, budgeting, and specifications for the new furniture (1965-1966) and the planning and installation of cable television in the new headquarters building (1966-1969). The files are arranged alphabetically.
  - 477 Madison Avenue -- Additional Office Space -- Memoranda and Estimates Re: Experimental Furniture, Nov 30, 1964-Mar 12, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - 477 Madison Avenue -- Experiments -- 20th Floor Trial Offices -- Notes, Memoranda, Plans, Sep 23, 1963-Mar 12, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - 477 Madison Avenue -- Painting, Construction and Redecorating Estimates, Feb 2-Mar 12, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - 477 Madison Avenue -- Schmid, Robert -- Correspondence Re: Alterations and Refurbishing, Nov 2, 1961-Feb 19, 1963 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - 477 Madison Avenue -- Termination of Lease, Services and Furniture Disposal, Jan 26, 1966-Mar 30, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Audiovisual -- Rosner TV -- Proposal and Lists (1 of 4), 1966-1969 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Audiovisual -- Rosner TV -- Stage Equipment Contract (2 of 4), 1967-1968 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Audiovisual -- Rosner TV -- Correspondence and Drawings (3 of 4), 1968 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Audiovisual -- Rosner TV -- CATV Installation (4 of 4), 1968-1969 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Carpets -- Lord and Adams -- Quotes for 10th and 11th Floors, Jun 15, 1966-Jul 12, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Herman Miller -- Price Quotations, 1966-1967 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - File Equipment -- Diebold, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Food Service Equipment -- Heifetz Metal Crafts, Inc., Jan 18-Mar 1, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Furniture and Equipment Needs -- Central Services -- Lists, Oct 18-Nov 22, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Furniture and Furnishings -- Memoranda Re: Planning, Budgets, Specifications, 1965-1966 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Furniture -- Bids, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Furniture -- Decorating -- Metro Decorators, Inc. -- Bills, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Furniture -- Design costs -- Budget and Floor Plans, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Furniture -- Experimental Mock-up -- 477 Madison Avenue 20th Floor -- R.H. McCarthy's File -- Irwin Miller Memorandum, 1963-1965 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Furniture -- Standards -- Estimates, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Furniture -- Specifications, Estimates, Correspondence Re: Purchases, Drawings (1 of 2), 1965-1967 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Furniture -- Specifications, Estimates, Correspondence Re: Purchases, Drawings (2 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Furniture -- Wall Alternative Selections -- Drawings, Jan 3, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Interior Design -- Summary of Commitments and Expenses, 1965 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Interior Design -- Correspondence and Memoranda Re: Furnishing Price Quotes and Specifications, Dec 20, 1965-Sep 16, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Irving and Casson -- Trading Desk Plans, Contract, Inventories, 1966-1968 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Lehigh Furniture Corp. -- Correspondence, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - M. Gerber Construction Co. -- Furniture Installation (cabinets, closets, etc.), 1967-1969 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - New Building -- Miscellaneous Desk and Equipment Requirements -- Correspondence and Memoranda Re: Desks, Telephones, etc., Feb-May 1967 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Sketches -- Credenza and Shelving (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Window Washing Equipment -- Skyclimber -- Illustrations, Jul 18, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Building Services, Bulk, 1964-1969 1951-1998 (bulk 1964-1969); 1964-1969; V (Box not specified)
  Series V. Building Services, 1951-1998 (bulk 1964-1969)
  Arranged alphabetically by subject, the Building Services series files include correspondence and sub-leases associated with the Foundation's departure from its office space at 477 Madison Avenue (1966-1968). Other files pertain to the outside use of the Foundation's new building facilities and the development of policies (1968-1970). In addition there are inventory sheets that were removed from boxes processed as part of the building plans preservation project of the late 1990s (1971-1998).
  - Accounting System -- Proposed, Feb 27, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Allied Handi-Man Company -- Proposal, Analysis, Correspondence, 1964-1967 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Analysis of 7th Floor Area, 1964 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Art -- Inventory from 477 Madison Avenue, Feb 23-Nov 1, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Art Program -- Memoranda and Correspondence Re: Art Purchases, Andrew Ritchie, 1966-1969 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Budget Control Operations -- Budget Report, 1965-1966 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Building Plans Project -- Accession Records -- Blueprints -- Memorandum and Records Transfer Inventories, Aug 10, 1974-Oct 7, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Building Plans Project -- Box Inventory Sheets, Jan 19, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Building Plans Project -- Box Inventory Sheets of Building Plans -- Old Copies, 1973-1998 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Building Plans Project -- Box Inventory Sheets, 1993-1995 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Building Plans Project -- Building Construction File Index -- Box Inventory Sheets, 1963-1969 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Building Plans Project -- Index of Ford Foundation Building Plans and Drawings [Paradox Database], Jul 18, 1997 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Building Plans Project -- Meeting Agenda, Blueprint Inventory, Nov 17, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Cable TV -- New York Telephone Co. -- Correspondence Re: Hookups, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Cash Register -- Proposal, Apr 7, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Certificates of Approval -- Re: Electrical, Window Washing, Mail Conveyor, etc., 1968 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Completion -- Claims -- Turner, Mills, etc. -- Correspondence and Memoranda Re: Outstanding Claims, 1967-1971 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence -- General, Jan 17, 1966-Nov 7, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence -- General -- Financial Reports, Litigation, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence -- Headquarters -- Miscellaneous, Jan 3, 1967-Jan 29, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence -- Miscellaneous (1 of 2), 1965-1966 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence -- Miscellaneous (2 of 2), 1966-1967 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence Re: Rosner TV to Phil Kemp, Apr 18-19, 1968 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence -- Reading File -- Re: Complaints, Turner Construction, Insurance, etc. (1 of 4), Feb-Nov 1964 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence -- Reading File -- Re: Park Department, Architects, Zoning, etc. (2 of 4), Dec 1964-Feb 1965 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence -- Reading File -- Chronological Correspondence of R.H. McCarthy (3 of 4), Mar 1965-Jan 1966 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence -- Reading File -- Chronological Correspondence of Robert E. Ashley (4 of 4), Feb-Dec 1966 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Critical Path Program -- Planning Handbook, Bar Chart, Method, 1964-1967 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Elevators -- Memorandum Re: Final Installation, Dec 5, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Exterminating Services -- Sameth Exterminating Co., Inc. -- Contract, Sep 3, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Fire Control Materials, Jun 11, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Fire Safety -- Permits, Approvals, Fire Communications System, 1974-1977 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Food Service -- New Building -- Memorandum, Jul 21, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Garage -- Memorandum Re: Parking Allocation, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Garden -- Correspondence Re: Landscaping Award, Invoices, Jun 4, 1968-Sep 30, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Index -- Storage Containers Sent by Architects of Shop Drawings by Contractors and Vendors, and Not Plans List, [1966]-1995 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Inter-Office Memoranda -- Miscellaneous -- Personal Mail, Design Meeting, etc., Dec 16, 1965-Jul 8, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Lists of Contractors, Manufacturers, Suppliers, Chronology of the Ford Foundation Headquarters, 196[7] (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Maintenance and Security -- Dominick G. Riley Detective Bureau, 1965-1968 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Meeting of Architects and Construction Groups, Jun 18, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous -- Memoranda and Quotations Re: Furnishings, etc. (1 of 2), 1965-1967 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous -- Memoranda and Quotations Re: Furnishings, etc. (2 of 2), 1967 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Move to New Building -- Move Coordination Committee Agenda, Plans, Related Correspondence, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Occupancy and Move -- Correspondence, Memoranda, Timetable Re: Move, 1967-1968 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Outside Use of Facilities -- Requests, Correspondence, Policy Development, 1968-1970 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Phil Kemp Building Files [microfilm], n.d. (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Policy for Contractor's Advertising -- Memoranda, Jan 2-Mar 6, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Receptionists -- Memoranda Re: Planning, Nov 25, 1965-Jul 28, 1966 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Restaurant Correspondence -- Photographs (separated) Re: Architectural Record Feb 1969 Article (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Security -- New Building Requirements -- Memoranda and Correspondence, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Staff Memoranda from Gertrude Winquist, Jul 1966-May 1968 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Lease -- 477 Madison Avenue -- Barbet & Weigert Advertising Inc. -- 16th Floor, Dec 20, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Lease -- 477 Madison Avenue -- City Investing Co. -- 19th Floor -- Lease and Correspondence Re: Litigation, Dec 11, 1967-Apr 15, 1970 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Lease -- 477 Madison Avenue -- Educational Facilities Labs, Inc. -- 20th Floor, Dec 1, 1967-Feb 12, 1968 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Lease -- 477 Madison Avenue -- Engelhard Industries -- 24th Floor, Jun 27, 1966 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Lease -- 477 Madison Avenue -- Esaress International Group -- 15th Floor, Apr 3, 1968 (Box 50, Folder 1)